craftulous.com 2016-08-22

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Service - Craftulous

## Disclaimers, Rules, Policies and stuffs.

  * unless otherwise noted, all original content, photos, and images (including the featured images displayed in the title sections of posts and pages) were created by me and are copyrighted. essentially, don’t jack my shiz. if you want permission to use my stuff or you want to purchase commercial usage rights for a photo or something like that, contact me and we’ll work something out.
  * any and all free-of-charge/complimentary original content that I make available for download (for personal or commercial use) is not covered under any warranty, explicit or implicit.
  * the stuff I write as well as any external links within posts are made available for entertainment and informational purposes only; and while I do my best to make sure any info I provide is accurate, I can’t make any guarantees.
  * I hate spam as much as you do. I won’t spam you. I won’t share your email address.
  * Winners’ contact information may be shared with prize sponsors for the purpose of prize fulfillment.

_Also see:[my disclosure policy](http://craftulous.com/disclosure-policy/ "Disclosure Policy")_

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [http://craftulous.com/contact](mailto:super+privacy@craftulous.com).

At [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) and how we use it.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/).  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….

  * Google
  * Amazon
  * Clickbank
  * Linkshare
  * ShareASale
  * Skimlinks

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:  [Privacy Policies](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policies).  
You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/)._

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

[http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/)’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: [Privacy Policy Links](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policy-links "Privacy Policy Links").

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

**Children’s Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that [http://craftulous.com](http://craftulous.com/) has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Thursday, June 19th, 2014.  
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._

### **Terms of Use**

While every effort is made to make sure that the information presented on this blog is accurate at the time of publishing, no guarantee is made as to the accuracy or efficacy of the information provided. In other words— do your due diligence!

### **Copyright Policy**

Unless otherwise noted, I, Kristina Quinones, am the legal copyright holder of all material on this blog and others cannot use it to reprint or publish without my explicit written consent.

### **Hold Harmless**

All the information provided on this blog is for entertainment purposes only, and I do not provide medical, legal or other professional advice. Using any of the information from your blog at their own risk. Again, I make every effort to make sure all the information I provide is true and accurate, but do your due diligence!

I reserve the right to update or change my blog completely, including changing the focus of the subject matter, closing it down completely, or changing the terms of use.

I am not responsible for the actions of advertisers or sponsors. Please be aware that if you purchase a product of service based upon a link from this blog, you must take action with that exact company to resolve any issues.

### **Letters to the Editor and Commenting Policy**

Comments on this blog are posted publicly, and I welcome open discussion! You have the right to use an alias or nickname instead of your real name when posting a comment.

I reserve the right to delete or block particularly vulgar, hateful, and spammy comments and messages at my discretion.

Emails and private messages (via Twitter, Facebook, etc.) are confidential, and I will not share or sell the email address that you use to make a comment or send me an email unless otherwise explicitly noted or required to do so by law (or if your messages and comments are so vile, abusive, hateful that I need to report you to the authorities). Let’s not go there!

### Giveaways

Location-specific eligibility rules vary based on the giveaway, and entry into any giveaway hosted on craftulous.com are void where such activity is prohibited. Any contact information collected is used solely for the purpose of contacting the winner(s) and fulfillment of prizes.

Winners’ contact information may be shared with prize sponsors for the purpose of prize fulfillment. If email addresses or other information is to be used for  _giveaway entries_ are to be shared with the sponsor(s), this information will be explicitly noted in the giveaway details.
